{
  "id": 201,
  "themeId": 2,
  "name": "Writing and Reading Color Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Red\"?",
      "options": [
        "Rose",
        "Rouge",
        "Led",
        "Bordeaux"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Rouge",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Yellow\"?",
      "options": [
        "Noir",
        "Jaune",
        "Maillot",
        "Rose"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Jaune",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Orange\"?",
      "options": [
        "Outre",
        "Bleu",
        "Orangeu",
        "Orange"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Orange",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Purple\"?",
      "options": [
        "Violet",
        "Marron",
        "Pomme",
        "Violette"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Violet",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Brown\"?",
      "options": [
        "Gris",
        "Ronde",
        "Marron",
        "Clair"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Marron",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Pink\"?",
      "options": [
        "Rose",
        "Rouge",
        "Rosse",
        "Rouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Rose",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Blue\"? (masculine singular)",
      "options": [
        "Beau",
        "Blueu",
        "Bleut√©",
        "Bleu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bleu",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Green\"? (feminine singular)",
      "options": [
        "Grasse",
        "Verte",
        "Vert",
        "Feuille"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Verte",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"White\"? (masculine singular)",
      "options": [
        "Blanche",
        "Blant",
        "Blanct",
        "Blanc"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Blanc",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Black\"? (feminine plural)",
      "options": [
        "Noire",
        "Noires",
        "Noirs",
        "Nuit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Noires",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}